<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Solutions on Asphalt Cutbacks Inc.</title>
    <link>https://zotos.github.io/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Solutions on Asphalt Cutbacks Inc.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://zotos.github.io/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Built Up Roofing</title>
      <link>https://zotos.github.io/services/bur/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zotos.github.io/services/bur/</guid>
      <description>Roofing asphalt is a widely used material for flat roofs, providing excellent protection against the elements and weather. One popular type of roofing system that utilizes asphalt is built-up roofing (BUR). BUR consists of multiple layers of reinforcing fabric, known as felts, that are bonded together with hot asphalt.
Built-Up Roofing: A Time-Tested Solution for Flat Roofs Built-up roofing (BUR) is a type of roofing system that has been used for over 100 years to provide durable and reliable protection for flat and low-sloped roofs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cutback Asphalt</title>
      <link>https://zotos.github.io/services/cutback/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zotos.github.io/services/cutback/</guid>
      <description>Cutback asphalt is a type of asphalt that has been blended with a solvent, usually a petroleum-based solvent, to make it more fluid and easier to apply. This type of asphalt is commonly used in a variety of applications, including pipe coating, industrial coatings, and roofing.
Common uses In pipe coating, cutback asphalt is applied to the surface of pipes to provide protection against corrosion and other environmental factors. The solvent in the asphalt helps to penetrate the surface of the pipe, creating a durable and long-lasting barrier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Industrial Specialties</title>
      <link>https://zotos.github.io/services/is/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zotos.github.io/services/is/</guid>
      <description>Industrial asphalts are versatile materials that can be used in various applications beyond paving and road construction. These applications include roofing, waterproofing, insulation, adhesives, and sealants, among others.
Roofing: Provides excellent protection against water damage and leaks Resistant to harsh weather conditions, such as high winds and extreme temperatures Can be used in built-up roofing systems, modified bitumen roofing, and other applications Waterproofing: Creates a barrier against moisture intrusion, preventing damage and deterioration of structures Provides long-lasting protection against water infiltration and leaks Can be used in various applications, including foundations, basements, tunnels, and more Insulation: Provides excellent thermal insulation properties, reducing heat loss and improving energy efficiency Can be used in various applications, including roofs, walls, and floors Offers superior sound insulation properties, reducing noise transmission Adhesives: Forms a strong bond between surfaces, providing reliable and long-lasting adhesion Resistant to water, heat, and chemicals, ensuring a durable bond Can be used in various applications, including flooring, roofing, and construction Sealants: Creates a barrier against moisture, preventing water infiltration and damage to structures Provides excellent weather resistance, protecting against UV rays, temperature changes, and other environmental factors Can be used in various applications, including windows, doors, roofs, and concrete joints At Asphalt Cutbacks, Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Blends</title>
      <link>https://zotos.github.io/services/custom/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zotos.github.io/services/custom/</guid>
      <description>At ACI, we understand that every project is unique and requires a specific blend of materials to achieve the desired results. That&amp;rsquo;s why we offer custom asphalt blends to meet the individual needs of our customers.
What are custom blends? Custom asphalt blends are mixtures of different types of asphalt and other materials that are tailored to meet specific project requirements. These blends are designed to enhance the performance and durability of asphalt-based products, providing long-lasting protection against the elements.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
